<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<itemrelease version="2.0">
  <item format="nl" id="884" version="13" bankkey="187">
    <attriblist>
      <attrib attid="itm_item_id">
        <name>Item: ITS ID</name>
        <val>884</val>
        <desc></desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_item_subject">
        <name>Item: Subject</name>
        <val>ELA</val>
        <desc></desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_item_desc">
        <name>Item: Item Description</name>
        <val>ELA.11.SR.2.W.01.xxx - SB OP</val>
        <desc></desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_FTUse">
        <name>Fieldtest Use</name>
        <val>PracTest::ELAG11::SP13 (26); PracTest::ELAG11::SP13::BRAILLE (35);</val>
        <desc></desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_OPUse">
        <name>Operational Use</name>
        <val></val>
        <desc></desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_att_Answer Key">
        <name>Item: Answer Key</name>
        <val>NL</val>
        <desc></desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_att_Grade">
        <name>Item: Grade</name>
        <val>11</val>
        <desc>11</desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_att_Item Format">
        <name>Item: Item Format</name>
        <val>NL</val>
        <desc>NL [3]</desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_att_Page Layout">
        <name>Item: Page Layout</name>
        <val>8</val>
        <desc>8 [3.2]</desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_att_Response Type">
        <name>Item: Response Type</name>
        <val>PlainText</val>
        <desc></desc>
      </attrib>
      <attrib attid="itm_att_Item Point">
        <name>Item: Item Point</name>
        <val>1 pt.</val>
        <desc>1 Point</desc>
      </attrib>
    </attriblist>
    <tutorial id="1078" bankkey="187" />
    <resourceslist />
    <statistic />
    <MachineRubric filename="Item_884_v13.nlx" />
    <content language="ENU" version="2.0" approvedVersion="13">
      <rationaleoptlist />
      <stem><![CDATA[<p style="">A student is writing a narrative for a creative writing class assignment. She has given her first paragraph to her teacher, who suggested she continue writing, including details in her narrative. Read the paragraph and the directions that follow.</p><p style="">&#xA0;</p><p style="margin-left:0.5in; margin-right:0.5in; text-indent:0.25in; ">The Fourth of July holiday has always been dear to my heart. Every year, my family gathers together at my aunt’s house for a celebration. Her house is not a mansion by the lake, nor does it have an astounding view; the people and the activities are what make the place so serene. We begin our afternoon by eating typical summer food. In the late afternoon, my cousins and I play baseball while our parents talk on the porch. In the evening, we eat together again and then watch the fireworks display put on by our town.</p><p style="">&#xA0;</p><p style="">Rewrite the paragraph using appropriate narrative strategies such as the inclusion of dialogue and vivid descriptions. &#xA0;</p>]]></stem>
      <rubriclist>
        <rubric scorepoint="2">
          <name>
        Rubric 2</name>
          <val><![CDATA[<p style="">A two-point response includes narrative strategies such as the inclusion of dialogue and vivid description.</p><ul style="padding-left:NaNem; "><li><p style="">provides appropriate and predominately specific details or evidence</p></li><li><p style="">uses appropriate word choices for intended audience and purpose </p></li></ul>]]></val>
        </rubric>
        <samplelist maxval="2" minval="2">
          <sample purpose="OtherExemplar" scorepoint="2">
            <name>2-Point Other Official Sample Answers
      </name>
            <annotation />
            <samplecontent><![CDATA[<p style="">Fried chicken, cornbread, potato salad. Seeing these foods on my baby cousin’s face tells me our family’s day has arrived: The Fourth at Aunt June’s. It’s no mansion or lakeview paradise, but it’s ours. Every Watson who can walk or be carried shows up on that day every year. Just hearing a few snippets of the parents’ conversation sends me flying into the field with my cousins, chasing a fly ball until it takes me halfway through Aunt June’s vegetable garden. You think she’d yell, but she goes for the ball too, and when we nearly collide, she always says “I said I had it!” But she’s laughing with me, and at night we share a blanket to watch the fireworks spark up from the nearest town. Aunt June makes it summertime, every year.</p>]]></samplecontent>
          </sample>
        </samplelist>
        <rubric scorepoint="1">
          <name>
        Rubric 1</name>
          <val><![CDATA[<p style="">A one-point response includes general details and some narrative strategies such as dialogue or description.</p><ul style="padding-left:NaNem; "><li><p style="">provi<span style="">des mostly general details and evidence, but may include extraneous or loosely related details</span></p></li><li><p style="">has a limited and predictable vocabulary that may not be consistently appropriate for the intended audience and purpose</p></li></ul>]]></val>
        </rubric>
        <samplelist maxval="1" minval="1">
          <sample purpose="Exemplar" scorepoint="1">
            <name>1-Point Official Sample Answer
      </name>
            <annotation />
            <samplecontent><![CDATA[<p style="">My aunt’s house is the place to go on the Fourth of July. It’s not a mansion by the lake, nor does it have an astounding view; it’s the people and the activities that make the place so serene. We begin our afternoon by eating watermelon, potato salad, and barbecued chicken. In the late afternoon, my cousins and I play baseball while our parents talk about last night’s game on the porch. In the evening, we eat leftovers and watch the fireworks shoot stars over our own piece of the sky.</p>]]></samplecontent>
          </sample>
        </samplelist>
        <rubric scorepoint="0">
          <name>
        Rubric 0</name>
          <val><![CDATA[<p style="">A response that does not include narrative strategies that enhance the story receives no credit.</p>]]></val>
        </rubric>
        <samplelist maxval="0" minval="0">
          <sample purpose="Exemplar" scorepoint="0">
            <name>0-Point Official Sample Answer
      </name>
            <annotation />
            <samplecontent><![CDATA[<p style="">I like the Fourth. It’s my favorite holiday, and I spend it with my family.</p>]]></samplecontent>
          </sample>
        </samplelist>
      </rubriclist>
      <attachmentlist>
        <attachment id="file1" type="BRF" subtype="contracted" file="item_884_enu_contracted.brf" />
        <attachment id="file2" type="BRF" subtype="uncontracted" file="item_884_enu_uncontracted.brf" />
      </attachmentlist>
    </content>
  </item>
</itemrelease>